Look at the gridlock bleeding in red
A million lost souls with a heavy tread
But we caught the ramp and we took the flight
Now we're cutting a line right through the night
Up on the overpass, elevated and free Leaving
the ghosts and the machinery A blur of neon in a
steady hum We're beating the rhythm of a
different drum Up on the overpass Watch us fly
The concrete ribbon is a perfect track
Got the pedal down and we're not looking back
Hear the frequency rising from the street below
But we're riding a current that they'll never
know
Up on the overpass, elevated and free Leaving
the ghost and the machinery A blur of neon in a
steady hum Repeating the rhythm of a different
drum Up on the overpass Watch us fly
Suspended in the air Without a single care The
altitude is climbing Perfect in our time
Up on the overpass, elevated and free Leaving
the ghosts and the machinery A blur of neon in its
steady hum Beating the rhythm of a different
drum Up on the overpass, watch us fly
High above the great head
WATCH US SLIDE